# Data fetched from Open Trivia DB
question_data = [
    {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Faust is a playable character in &quot;Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Centripedal force is an apparent force that acts outward on a body moving around a center, arising from the body&#039;s inertia.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Liechtenstein does not have an airport.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Nickelodeon rejected the pilot to Adventure Time.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Television","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The French Kingdom helped the United States gain their independence over Great Britain during the Revolutionary War.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Nutcracker Suite was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The game &quot;Jetpack Joyride&quot; was created by &quot;Redbrick Studios&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}
    ]